http://www.abgile.com/privacy-policy

Skip to contentAuto Quote Homeowner Quote Condo Quote Renters Quote
Insurance Quotes
Auto QuoteHomeowner QuoteCondo QuoteRenters QuoteClaimsAccidentsMore…Claims Accidents
603-643-4540 PO Box 66Hanover, NH 03755 Toggle navigation
HomeInsuranceClaims & ServiceBlogAboutContactPrivacy Policy A. B. Gile, Inc.Privacy PolicyA.B. Gile, Inc. has been serving the insurance needs of our customers and friends for over 140 years. To continue to provide innovative products and services that respond to your insurance needs, we may collect certain personal information about you. It is important for you to realize that A.B. Gile, inc. is committed to protecting your privacy rights. We acknowledge your right to keep your own financial information confidential and, because of this, we have created this document to explain our privacy policy to you. In addition, we are complying with both state and federal laws which require insurance agencies (as well as all financial institutions) to notify you, our valued customers, about how we intend to treat your nonpublic personal financial information that you have entrusted us with.Information we collect: We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:Information we receive from you on applications or other formsInformation about your transactions with us, our affiliates or othersInformation we receive from a consumer reporting agencyUnless it is specifically stated otherwise in an amended Privacy Policy Notice, no additional information will be collected from you.Information we may disclose to third parties: We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law.Our practices regarding information confidentiality and security: We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. Reservation of the right to disclose information in unforeseen circumstances: In the event that the stockholder(s) of A.B. Gile, Inc. decide to sell or transfer their ownership interest in the business, they reserve the right to sell or transfer your information (including but not limited to your address, name, age, sex, zip code, state and country of residency and other information that you provide through communications) to a third party entity that 1) concentrates its business in a similar practice or service; 2) agrees to be A.B. Gile’s successor in interest with regard to the maintenance and protection of the information collected; and 3) agrees to the obligations of this privacy statement. Get a QuoteGive us some info and we'll get quotes from multiple companies.Get a Quote
Toggle Dropdown AutoHomeownerLifeMotorcycleBusinessMore…Insurance Partners
From Our Blog Don’t Delay — Start Thinking About Winterizing Your RV Today December 4, 2020
10 Things to do to Prepare Your Home for Fall November 6, 2020
It’s Back-to-School Time — Is Your House Ready? October 2, 2020
Connect OnlineAbout Us A. B. Gile, Inc. is an independent insurance agency located in West Lebanon, New Hampshire. Give us a call, stop by, or request a quote online to find out how much we can save you on your insurance.HomeAboutContactSitemapRecent Articles Don’t Delay — Start Thinking About Winterizing Your RV Today December 4, 2020
10 Things to do to Prepare Your Home for Fall November 6, 2020
It’s Back-to-School Time — Is Your House Ready? October 2, 2020 Quick LinksAbout UsContact UsService CenterInsurance ProductsGet an Insurance QuoteCompanies We RepresentStaff DirectoryContact Us 377 North Main StreetWest Lebanon, NH 03784 603-643-4540 603-643-6382 info [at] abgile [dot] com info [at] abgile [dot] com Mon-Fri 8am-4:30pm © 2020 A. B. Gile, Inc. | Search | Privacy | Disclaimer | Website by BT
